My name is Donovan Maslin and I am
[music] creating black history.
>> You mean everything. You know, at 29
when I took over, this was a dream and
it came to fruition. It wasn't
immediately, but now we finally here and
my testimony [music] going to be loud.
Oh, it means just creating and
continuing the the excellence that that
we have um that has been bestowed upon
us uh through the trailblazing of
[music] the our ancestors and
predecessors before us and that we want
to make sure that we continue [music]
the legacy uh and instilling that into
our young African-American men that we
come across and uh so that they can
continue
>> [music]
>> uh the torch. Oh man, it was uh it's a
phenomenal feeling, you know, that we
have accomplished u some major
milestones [music] this year. uh we set
out, you know, as this was the main
goal. [music] Um you know, we just took
it one game at a time, but ultimately,
you know, we had to, you know, take
advantage of our opportunities, take
advantage of our matchup, but you know,
to ultimately come out with [music] the
win was was um phenomenal. It was uh
triumphant. [music] You know, the kids
never gave up. They continued to fight
throughout. Um you know, we knew going
into the season that, you know, it would
come down to the [music] wire uh with
either us Northwestern or Central. And
um you know, we were able to, you know,
figure out a game plan to control them
[music] offensively and then get us some
points um you know, in the box and be
able to come out on top. And you know,
just ultimately just, you know,
being able [music] to do it undefeated
is is is um is special, man. Like you
you only dream of it as coaches. [music]
Um, but to actually come out and do it
and to be a part of it, you know, it's
it's
his words can't really describe [music]
the feeling that, you know, we have as a
staff, as a team, you know, as players.
Um, to be one of the best in the state,
you know, in in in the history of
[music]
high school football is is is something,
you know, special. Uh, man, it was so
many people that um that played a major
major important part. [music] You know,
I I I can't start without, you know,
mentioning my father. you know, he was
an int intricate [music] part in who I
am and what I've been able to
accomplish, uh, laying the foundations
of who who, you know, manhood and how to
[music] be a man. Coach Cedric Thornton,
uh, once I got into the high school. Uh,
Roy Dawkins, uh, high school and
college. Um, Coach Richardson at
Highlands, [music] while while I was
there, he was definitely a person that
believed in me, uh, who gave me the mot,
you know, the the confidence [music] in
in instilling that, you know, I can play
at the next level. And then, you know,
of course, at Pop Warner, man, it was
[music] so many people. Coach Ronnie
Meyer, uh, Coach Joover, Coach Rod, you
know, all of those young men [music]
were great, uh, people that, you know,
played a major part. And also, Coach
Charles Owens, you know, he [music] was
another guy that was very important to,
uh, who I am as a person. It it means a
lot, you So it means that you know our
purpose uh here on earth um you know is
to [music] be right here in Viking land
you know to uh instill [music] into
everybody else you know family love um
[music] support dedication and
commitment and um you know our family
has been built on that you know from the
ground up you know [music] ever since my
grandparents you know we're in
Jacksonville uh my family is just
[music] big on you know being a family
orient spirited group and uh that's the
that's the same type of leg legacy we
want to make sure that we leave when
we're done [music] you know coaching
here but we're always going to continue
to support is that you know in order for
you know our [music] brand to continue
our tradition to continue we have to be
family first and uh have [music] great
relationships with you know everybody
that we come across uh nobody's bigger
than the program and that we're all
working for the greater good of kids. Oh
man, just [music]
um preparation, opportunity, um making
sure that in every aspect of life that
you prepared, you know, to your to
[music] the best of your ability and
that when your opportunity presents
itself, be able to take advantage of it.
[music] Um two things that I feel, you
know, as as young men, you know, you
have to be ready for the opportunity,
but you ultimately have to be prepared
for it [music] as well so that you can
reap the benefits of what you're trying
to do. Shout out to the Jaguars, you
know, organization, the foundations that
they have that's, [music] you know,
geared and predicated to um helping the
inner city schools and not just in the
city schools, but schools all around the
community uh with, you know, the 707
[music]
uh inviting, you know, schools to the
football games on Sundays. Uh it's been
it's been phenomenal feeling because a
lot of kids don't have the opportunity
to go [music]
uh to NFL games and, you know, just to
be able to get the experience right here
in Jacksonville. Um, you do you guys do
a great job. Uh, we want to make sure we
appreciate you guys for sending, you
know, me, [music] you know, to the Super
Bowl. It's going to be a phenomenal
experience. And, you know, God bless.
>> [music]